

CONTACT

- +6282118923691
- azmiiskandar@@gmail.com
- @m.azmiiskndr

EDUCATION

Bina Sarana Informatika University

2019-2022 GPA : 3.98

EXPERTISE

- HTML
- CSS
- AJAX
- JQUERY
- JAVASCRIPT
- PHP
- Codeigniter
- Laravel
- Livewire
- Repository Pattern
- MySQL
- Adobe Photoshop

MOCH AZMI ISKANDAR WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

My name is Azmi. I am 21 years old. I was graduated from Bina Sarana Informatika University majoring in Information System (IS) in 2022 after receiving a scholarship as the finalist of Students Competion of Inovation and Business. I have expertise in making websites, programing language (e.g. HTML, CSS, PHP, Codeigniter 3, Laravel, and MySQL). I am certified as a software developer and programmer in 2022. In addition, I have 1 year of professional experience in the field of PHP development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Staff Programmer
 - PT. Varnion Technology Semesta | Feb Present
- PHP Programmer
 - PT. FTF Globalindo | Nov Feb 2023
- PHP Developer (Mahasiswa Intern)
 - Nusantara Beta Studio Okt Nov 2022
- Website Developer
 - Devifo Studio| 2020-2021
- Photographer and Editor
 - RM Photo Studio | 2018-2019

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

- Students Competition of Innovation and Business (KIBM)
 - Finalist | 2020

CERTIFICATE OF COMPETENCES

- Software Developer and Programmer
 - No. 6210 2514 5 0001713 2022
- Basic Programming JavaScript
 - No. 10P85QYJVPQK | Dicoding.com
- Cloud Practitioner Essentials Certificate
 - No. L4PQ6D0D7P01 | Dicoding.com